Drums in my head just what i need oh i bet you
wondered how a new batch of hands to make
me blue with some honor god you knew before
between the two of us guys you know i love
you more it took me by surprise i must say
when i found out yesterday don't you know
that i heard through the grapevine not much
longer would you be my,uh do the grape
vernon i doesn't about to lose my mind honey
well,i know a man it's a bull to cry but
these tears i can't hold and sign losing
you in my life you see house you mean that
much to me you could have tow me ourself that
you love someone else they stand ahead
do the great van not much longer would you
be my i do the great van and i'm just about
to lose my mind been well people say believe
half of what you see son and none of what
you hear but i can't been confused if it's
true please tell me there do you let let
me go for the other guy you love before don't
you know through the great van not much
longer would you be my baby her through the
grape by who just about to lose my mind
hot here honey honey,i know that you let
me go santa do the great van.Who had it through
the grapevine,who are due the grape?